Familia, familia, familia
Build a wealth and then leave it to the
I'm the one that's been waited on by
Blood so cold that it froze in my veins
Only runs when there's money to be made
Time been invested, baby, I've paid
With the nights that I stayed up late, wide awake
To be real, it's not a thrill I seek
More like a table with family and a meal we couldn't eat
Don't want no wagon till my sister has three
A Richard Millie for the time I've spent chasing the G's
I wear time on my wrist for the years I gave
Been stepping on the road I've paved
Dont't rush, I'm respecting the wait
Learned patience from pressure, faith from the wait
Can't cut, no shortcuts to make
Zero fucks left to give, only millions to make
Can't cut no shortcuts to make
When I'm gone what I leave feeds the bloodline
I leave it to the familia, familia, familia
Familia, familia, familia